<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DietChart</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="didn_t_get_otp_resend">Didn\'t get OTP? <b>Resend</b></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_angry_gain">AngryGainActivity</string>
    <string name="your_suitable_diet_plan_is_here">Your Suitable Diet Plan is Here,</string>
    <string name="_1_gain_weight">1. How to Gain Weight the Healthy Way</string>
    <string name="if_you_want_to_gain_weight_">●If you want to gain weight, it’s very important to do it right.\n ●Binging on soda and donuts may help you gain weight, but it can destroy your health at the same time.\n ●If you’re underweight, you want to gain a balanced amount of muscle mass and subcutaneous fat rather than a lot of unhealthy belly fat.\n ●There are plenty of normal-weight people who get type 2 diabetes, heart disease and other health problems often associated with obesity\n ●Therefore, it’s absolutely essential to eat healthy foods and live an overall healthy lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="_2_gain_weight">2. Eat More Calories Than Your Body Burns</string>
    <string name="_3_angry_gain_weight">3. Eat Plenty of Protein</string>
    <string name="_4_angry_gain_weight">4. Fill up on Plenty of Carbs and Fat and Eat at Least 3 Times per Day</string>
    <string name="_5_angry_gain_weight">5. Lift Heavy Weights and Improve Your Strength</string>
    <string name="_6_angry_gain_weight">6. Here are some energy-dense foods that are perfect for gaining weight</string>
    <string name="the_most_important_thing_you_can_do_to_gain_weight_">●The most important thing you can do to gain weight is to create a calorie surplus, meaning you eat more calories than your body needs.\n ●You can determine your calorie needs using this calorie calculator or just simply multiply your weight by 29 you will know how much calories ypur body required to stay maintenance.\n ●If you want to gain weight slowly and steadily, aim for 300–500 calories more than you burn each day according to the calculator.\n ●If you want to gain weight fast, aim for around 700–1,000 calories above your maintenance level.\n ●Keep in mind that calorie calculators only provide estimates. Your needs may vary by several hundred calories per day, give or take.\n ●You don’t need to count calories for the rest of your life, but it helps to do it for the first few days or weeks to get a feel for how many calories you’re eating.\n</string>
    <string name="the_single_most_important_nutrient_">●The single most important nutrient for gaining healthy weight is protein.\n ●Muscle is made of protein and without it most of those extra calories may end up as body fat.\n ●Studies show that during periods of overfeeding, a high-protein diet causes many of the extra calories to be turned into muscle.\n ●However, keep in mind that protein is a double-edged sword. It’s also highly filling, which may reduce your hunger and appetite significantly, making it harder to get in enough calories.\n ●Aim for 0.7–1 grams of protein per pound of body weight (1.5–2.2 grams of protein per kilogram). You can even go above that if your calorie intake is very high.\n ●High-protein foods include meats, fish, eggs, many dairy products, legumes, nuts and others. Protein supplements like whey protein can also be useful if you struggle to get enough protein in your diet.</string>
    <string name="eat_plenty_of_high_carb_and_high_fat_foods_">●Eat plenty of high-carb and high-fat foods if weight gain is a priority for you. It is best to eat plenty of protein, fat and carbs at each meal.\n ●It is also a bad idea to do intermittent fasting. This is useful for weight loss and health improvement but can make it much harder to eat enough calories to gain weight.\n ●Make sure to eat at least three meals per day and try to add in energy-dense snacks whenever possible.</string>
    <string name="to_make_sure_that_the_excess_calories_go_to_your_muscles_i">●To make sure that the excess calories go to your muscles instead of just your fat cells, it’s absolutely crucial to lift weights.\n ●Go to a gym and lift 2–4 times per week. Lift heavy and try to increase the weights and volume over time.\n ●If you’re completely out of shape or new to training, consider hiring a qualified personal trainer to help you get started.\n ●You may also want to consult with a doctor if you have skeletal problems or any medical issue.\n ●It’s probably best to take it easy on the cardio for now — focus mostly on the weights\n ●Doing some cardio is fine to improve fitness and well-being, but don’t do so much that you end up burning all the additional calories you’re eating.</string>
    <string name="combining_a_high_calorie_intake_with_heavy_strength_training_">●Combining a high calorie intake with heavy strength training are the two most important factors such as, Nuts: Almonds, walnuts, macadamia nuts, peanuts, etc.\n Dried fruit: Raisins, dates, prunes and others.\n High-fat dairy: Whole milk, full-fat yogurt, cheese, cream.\n Fats and oils: Extra virgin olive oil and avocado oil.\n Grains: Whole grains like oats and brown rice.\n Meat: Chicken, beef, pork, lamb, etc. Choose fattier cuts.\n Tubers: Potatoes, sweet potatoes and yams.\n Dark chocolate, avocados, peanut butter, coconut milk, granola, trail mixes.\n</string>
    <string name="being_on_a_diet_">[Being on a diet could often reduce tolerance levels, but luckily, there are certain food items that help calm the temper without affecting the weight loss regime.]</string>
    <string name="_1_eating_breakfast_will_help_you_">1. Eating breakfast will help you start your day with plenty of energy. Don\'t ruin your breakfast with high-fat and high-calorie foods. Choose some protein and fiber for your breakfast; breakfast is also a good time to eat some fresh fruit.</string>
    <string name="_2_eat_regular_meals_eating_at_regular_times_">2. Eat regular meals Eating at regular times during the day helps burn calories at a faster rate. It also reduces the temptation to snack on foods high in fat and sugar. Consume foods as close as possible to how they look in nature. For example, an orange is less processed and closer to nature than orange juice.</string>
    <string name="_3_eat_plenty_of_fruit_and_veg_">3. Eat plenty of fruit and veg Fruit and veg are low in calories and fat, and high in fibre – 3 essential ingredients for successful weight loss. They also contain plenty of vitamins and minerals. Eat plenty of dopamine-building foods, such as fish, poultry, eggs, and leafy greens.</string>
    <string name="_4_get_more_active_being_active_">4. Get more active Being active is key to losing weight and keeping it off. As well as providing lots of health benefits, exercise can help burn off the excess calories you cannot lose through diet alone.</string>
    <string name="_5_drink_plenty_of_water_people_">5. Drink plenty of water People sometimes confuse thirst with hunger. You can end up consuming extra calories when a glass of water is really what you need.</string>
    <string name="_6_eat_high_fibre_foods_foods_">6. Eat high fibre foods Foods containing lots of fibre can help keep you feeling full, which is perfect for losing weight. Fibre is only found in food from plants, such as fruit and veg, oats, wholegrain bread, brown rice and pasta, and beans, peas and lentils.</string>
    <string name="_7_read_food_labels_knowing_">7. Read food labels Knowing how to read food labels can help you choose healthier options. Use the calorie information to work out how a particular food fits into your daily calorie allowance on the weight loss plan. Get your vitamin D level checked. Low levels of vitamin D are associated with depression and mood disorders. Vitamin D can be found in fatty fish, egg yolks, liver and sunshine.</string>
    <string name="_8_beside_the_above_diet_keep_in_mind_the_following_points_">8. Beside the above diet keep in mind the following points- • Avoid heavy dinner; maintain at least 2 to 3 hours of gap between meal and sleep. • Replace cold drinks with coconut water, vegetable soup or butter milk • Drink at least 2 to 3 liters of water everyday • Fibre is excellent for weight loss , so consume more of raw vegetables and fruits • All carbs are not bad; avoid simple carbs like sugar, sweet and processed food. • Never skip meals. • Avoid Bakery products. • Replace Chicken Tikka with Chicken Salami • Avoid taking water along with the meal.</string>
    <string name="_1_load_your_plate_with_mood_supporting_foods_">1. Load your plate with mood-supporting foods by eating a rainbow of fruits and vegetables.</string>
    <string name="_2_consume_foods_as_close_as_possible_to_how_they_look_in_nature_">2. Consume foods as close as possible to how they look in nature.\nFor example, an orange is less processed and closer to nature than orange juice.</string>
    <string name="_3_eat_plenty_of_dopamine_building_foods_">3. Eat plenty of dopamine-building foods,\nSuch as fish, poultry, eggs, and leafy greens.</string>
    <string name="_4_increase_intake_of_omega_3_">4. Increase intake of omega-3 fatty acids, found in fish, flaxseed, chia seeds and walnuts, to help fight off feelings of depression.</string>
    <string name="_5_sprinkle_in_magnesium_rich_foods_">5. Sprinkle in magnesium-rich foods, which support sleep. Foods high in magnesium include almonds, spinach, pumpkin seeds and sunflower seeds.x</string>
    <string name="_6_limit_added_sugars_choose_">6. Limit added sugars. Choose no-sugar-added varieties of foods when possible. Have fruit for dessert more often than sugar-sweetened treats.</string>
    <string name="_7_get_your_vitamin_d_level_checked_">7. Get your vitamin D level checked. Low levels of vitamin D are associated with depression and mood disorders. Vitamin D can be found in fatty fish, egg yolks, liver and sunshine</string>
    <string name="overall_remember_that_the_key_is_balance_a_diet_">Overall, remember that the key is balance. A diet that contains a healthy amount of whole foods with a variety of nutrients can help you to feel more calm and more content.</string>
    <string name="day_1_lazy_gain">DAY 1</string>
    <string name="day_2_lazy_gain">DAY 2</string>
    <string name="day_3_lazy_gain">DAY 3</string>
    <string name="day_4_lazy_gain">DAY 4</string>
    <string name="day_5_lazy_gain">DAY 5</string>
    <string name="day_6_lazy_gain">DAY 6</string>
    <string name="day_7_lazy_gain">DAY 7</string>
    <string name="breakfast_1_">●Breakfast - 1 katori corn mix vegetable upma with 1 cup milk with 1 tsp chironji in it.\n●Mid-day meal – 1 katori seasonal fruit with pinch of cinnamon powderln\n●Lunch – 2 wheat roti with 1 katori soya masala curry, 1 tbsp. mint chutney\n●Snacks – 1 katori sprouts chaat\n●Dinner – 1 sweet potato cheese wrap with 1tblsp mint chutney</string>
    <string name="breakfast_1_paneer_vegetable_">●Breakfast – 1 paneer vegetable sandwich\n ●Mid-day meal – 1 katori roasted poha chiwda with added peanut\n ●Lunch – 2 paneer mix vegetable paratha with 1 bowl tur dal\n ●Snacks – 1 katori boiled cheesy sweet corn\n ●Dinner – 1 katori soya masala pulao</string>
    <string name="breakfast_2_panchmel_dal_dosa_">●Breakfast – 2 panchmel dal dosa with 1tblsp green chutney\n ●Mid-day meal – 1 boiled potato with pinch of black pepper ( 1 med size)\n ●Lunch – 2 wheat roti with 1 katori mix sprouts usal, 1 katori salad\n ●Snacks – 1 banana date milkshake\n ●Dinner – 1 katori ragda pattice (3 pattice)</string>
    <string name="breakfast_1_katori_">●Breakfast – 1 katori aloo peas poha, 1 cup milk\n ●Mid-day meal – 1 glass almond milkshake\n ●Lunch – 2 aloo methi paratha, 1 katori matki usal, 1 katori daliya kheer\n ●Snacks – 1 katori kurmura ground chiwda, 1 cup milk with 1 tsp almond powder\n ●Dinner – 1 rajmah tikki roll, 1 tblsp avocado dip\n</string>
    <string name="breakfast_4_paneer_cheese_mix_veg_">●Breakfast – 4 paneer cheese mix veg tikki with mint dip\n ●Mid-day meal – 1 cup almond milk apricot milkshake\n ●Lunch – 1 bowl chole pulao with 1 katori mix vegetable curry\n ●Snacks – 4 muthiyas, 1 cup milk\n ●Dinner – 2 palak masala dosa with 1 katori drumstick leaves</string>
    <string name="breakfast_1_katori_oats_porridge_">●Breakfast – 1 katori oats porridge with added dry fruits\n ●Mid-day meal – 1 glass mango almond smoothie\n ●Lunch – 2 wheat roti with 1 katori aloo peas curryln ●Snacks – 1 katori bhel with veggies and groundnuts\n ●Dinner – 1 cheese vegetable grilled sandwich with 1 tbsp mint chutey</string>
    <string name="breakfast_1_cucumber_rajgeera_">●Breakfast – 1 cucumber rajgeera singhada Thalipeeth with 1 katori curd\n ●Mid-day meal – 1 katori sevai kheer\n ●Lunch – 1 katori soya masala with 2 palak paratha\n ●Snacks – 1 glass mix dryfruits milkshake\n ●Dinner - 1 katori jeera rice with panchmel dal tadka</string>
    <string name="_1_lazy_lose">1. Cut down your portions</string>
    <string name="day_2_lazy_lose">2. Practice mindful eating</string>
    <string name="day_3_lazy_lose">3. Snack on nuts</string>
    <string name="day_4_lazy_lose">4. Eat more pulses</string>
    <string name="day_5_lazy_lose">5. Lower your room temperature</string>
    <string name="day_6_lazy_lose">6. Have your soup or salad first</string>
    <string name="day_7_lazy_lose">7. Get an extra cup of coffee</string>
    <string name="day_8_lazy_lose">8. Eat spicy food</string>
    <string name="day_9_lazy_lose">9. Drink green tea</string>
    <string name="day_10_lazy_lose">10. Think “half”</string>
    <string name="day_11_lazy_lose">11. Walk more.</string>
    <string name="you_don_t_need_to_completely_cut_out_foods_you_enjoy_whether_it_s_carbs_or_fats_denying_yourself_your_favorite_foods_may_only_make_your_cravings_worse_instead_cut_down_on_your_portions_and_balance_out_unhealthy_foods_with_healthier_foods_that_contain_fewer_calories_and_more_fiber">You don’t need to completely cut out foods you enjoy, whether it’s carbs or fats. Denying yourself your favorite foods may only make your cravings worse. Instead, cut down on your portions and balance out unhealthy foods with healthier foods that contain fewer calories and more fiber.</string>
    <string name="while_you_have_your_meals_or_even_your_snacks_try_to_pay_attention_to_the_look_smell_taste_and_feel_of_your_food_as_well_as_to_your_chewing_and_swallowing_being_fully_engaged_in_the_act_of_eating_will_help_you_be_more_in_tune_with_your_body_and_notice_when_you_are_actually_full_this_may_prevent_you_from_overeating">While you have your meals or even your snacks, try to pay attention to the look, smell, taste, and feel of your food, as well as to your chewing and swallowing. Being fully engaged in the act of eating will help you be more in tune with your body and notice when you are actually full/ This may prevent you from overeating.</string>
    <string name="instead_of_snacking_on_calorie_dense_food_make_it_a_habit_to_eat_nuts_especially_walnuts_and_almonds_they_can_make_you_feel_fuller_for_longer_so_that_you_eat_less_during_your_next_meal">Instead of snacking on calorie-dense food, make it a habit to eat nuts, especially walnuts and almonds. They can make you feel fuller for longer so that you eat less during your next meal.</string>
    <string name="like_nuts_pulses_such_as_beans_peas_chickpeas_and_lentils_keep_you_feeling_satiated_and_help_you_go_longer_between_meals">Like nuts, pulses such as beans, peas, chickpeas, and lentils keep you feeling satiated and help you go longer between meals.</string>
    <string name="lowering_your_room_temperature_to_66_f_at_night_can_help_you_burn_fat_as_your_body_needs_to_work_a_little_harder_to_keep_you_warm">Lowering your room temperature to 66 F at night can help you burn fat, as your body needs to work a little harder to keep you warm.</string>
    <string name="try_eating_a_salad_or_soup_before_your_main_course_this_can_fill_you_up_so_that_you_end_up_eating_less_of_your_main_course">Try eating a salad or soup before your main course. This can fill you up so that you end up eating less of your main course.</string>
    <string name="a_2020_study_published_in_the_journal_of_nutrition_found_that_women_who_consumed_2_3_cups_of_coffee_a_day_had_less_accumulation_of_fat_in_the_body_including_in_the_abdomen">A 2020 study published in The Journal of Nutrition found that women who consumed 2-3 cups of coffee a day had less accumulation of fat in the body, including in the abdomen.</string>
    <string name="let_s_make_a_thai_dish_tonight_yes_spicy_foods_have_been_known_to_speed_up_your_metabolism_so_add_a_little_cayenne_pepper_to_that_dish_plus_it_may_be_so_spicy_that_you_end_up_eating_a_little_less">Let’s make a Thai dish tonight! Yes spicy foods have been known to speed up your metabolism so add a little cayenne pepper to that dish. Plus it may be so spicy that you end up eating a little less.</string>
    <string name="green_tea_is_loaded_with_antioxidants_and_other_substances_that_help_boost_your_metabolism_studies_have_shown_that_there_are_active_components_in_green_tea_that_help_break_down_fat">Green tea is loaded with antioxidants and other substances that help boost your metabolism. Studies have shown that there are active components in green tea that help break down fat.</string>
    <string name="ok_so_i_said_this_was_the_lazy_person_guide_i_didn_t_say_you_had_to_go_to_the_gym_but_did_you_know_simply_by_adding_another_1000_2000_steps_to_your_day_can_actually_benefit_you_try_it_out">Ok, so I said this was the lazy person guide. I didn’t say you had to go to the gym, but did you know simply by adding another 1000-2000 steps to your day can actually benefit you? Try it out.</string>
    <string name="don_t_want_to_count_calories_that_s_fine_try_the_half_method_following_the_half_method_helps_you_practice_portion_control_so_that_you_can_save_yourself_the_extra_300_calories_that_you_don_t_need">Don’t want to count calories? That’s fine. Try the half method. Following the half method helps you practice portion control so that you can save yourself the extra 300 calories that you don’t need.</string>
    <string name="pre_breakfast_snack">Pre-breakfast snack</string>
    <string name="consume_a_fistful_of_soaked_almonds_and_walnuts_if_you_can_t_soak_the_dry_fruits_overnight_grab_a_banana">Consume a fistful of soaked almonds and walnuts. If you can\'t soak the dry fruits overnight, grab a banana.</string>
    <string name="breakfast_snack_">Breakfast snack</string>
    <string name="about_30_45_minutes_after_eating_the_nuts_you_may_have_your_breakfast_have_a_whole_wheat_bread_sandwich_or_two_stuffed_parathas_made_of_whole_wheat_or_multigrain_atta_nif_you_are_a_non_vegetarian_have_two_plain_parathas_with_green_chutney_and_one_boiled_egg_or_egg_paratha_you_may_even_have_one_of_the_following_recipes_n_3_4_ragi_idlis_small_sized_idlis_with_chutney_and_sambhar_n_a_bowl_full_of_mixed_vegetable_poha_or_sooji_upma_n_2moong_dal_chila_n_3_4_medium_sized_pieces_of_dhokla_khamni">About 30 -45 minutes after eating the nuts, you may have your breakfast. Have a whole wheat bread sandwich or two stuffed parathas made of whole wheat or multigrain atta.\nIf you are a non-vegetarian, have two plain parathas with green chutney and one boiled egg or egg paratha. You may even have one of the following recipes:\n 3-4 ragi idlis (small-sized idlis) with chutney and sambhar\n A bowl full of mixed vegetable poha or sooji upma\n 2Moong Dal Chila\n 3-4 medium-sized pieces of Dhokla (Khamni)</string>
    <string name="lunch">Lunch</string>
    <string name="have_your_lunch_between_1_to_2_pm_focus_on_foods_that_are_rich_in_lean_protein_have_tofu_soya_beans_soya_chunks_or_nuggets_lentils_and_legumes_like_rajma_etc_you_can_have_two_whole_wheat_atta_or_soya_atta_rotis_one_sabzi_vegetable_curry_some_fresh_vegetable_salads_tomatoes_cucumber_etc_one_chana_curry_or_any_other_legume_a_small_bowl_of_curd_or_a_glass_of_buttermilk_if_you_are_a_non_vegetarian_you_may_have_fish_or_chicken_preparation_avoid_red_meat">Have your lunch between 1 to 2 PM. Focus on foods that are rich in lean protein. Have tofu, soya beans, soya chunks or nuggets, lentils and legumes like rajma etc. You can have two whole-wheat atta or soya atta rotis, one sabzi (vegetable curry), some fresh vegetable salads (tomatoes, cucumber etc.), one chana curry or any other legume, a small bowl of curd or a glass of buttermilk. If you are a non-vegetarian, you may have fish or chicken preparation. Avoid red meat.</string>
    <string name="tea_time_snack">Tea time snack</string>
    <string name="have_baked_ragi_or_soya_chaklis_or_dry_fruits_chikki">Have baked ragi or soya chaklis or dry fruits chikki.</string>
    <string name="pre_dinner_meal">Pre-dinner meal</string>
    <string name="have_a_fistful_of_roasted_nuts_a_glass_of_fresh_fruit_juice_or_a_bowl_of_vegetable_soup">Have a fistful of roasted nuts, a glass of fresh fruit juice or a bowl of vegetable soup.</string>
    <string name="dinner">Dinner</string>
    <string name="if_you_sleep_at_about_10_pm_then_eat_your_meal_at_around_8_pm_you_may_have_for_oats_or_dalia_khichdi_or_two_rotis_and_a_sabzi_with_some_fresh_salads">If you sleep at about 10 PM, then eat your meal at around 8 PM. You may have for oats or dalia khichdi or two rotis and a sabzi with some fresh salads.</string>


</resources>